const STORE = {
  questions: [//1
    {
      question: "To open the gate to Moria, Gandalf says the Elvish word for __________.",
      options: [
        "Enter", 
        "Friend", 
        "Dwarf", 
        "Hello"
      ],
      answer: "Friend"
    },
    //2
    {
      question: "At the beginning of 'The Fellowship of the Ring', Bilbo is celebrating his birthday. How old is he?",
      options: [
        "88",
        "93", 
        "120",
        "111"
      ],
      answer: "111"
    },
    //3
    {
      question: "In Mordor, what kind of food does Frodo say he can't remember the taste of?",
      options: [
        "Bread", 
        "Cheese", 
      "Strawberries", 
        "Mushrooms"
      ],
      answer: "Strawberries"
    },
    //4
    {
      question: "Who became King of Rohan after Theoden met his demise in battle?", 
      options: [
        "Eowyn", 
        "Eomer", 
        "Grimer", 
        "Eorl"],
      answer: "Eomer"
    },
    //5
    {
      question: "Where does the Fellowship of the Ring break up?",
      options: [
        "Moria", 
        "Mirkwood", 
        "Isengard", 
        "Amon Hen"
      ],
      answer: "Amon Hen"
    },
    //6
    {
      question: "How many wizards are there in Middle Earth?",
      options: [
        "1", 
        "2", 
        "3", 
        "5"
      ],
      answer: "5"
    },
    //7
    {
      question: "Who rides ahead with Frodo to Rivendell after he is hit at Weathertop?",
      options: [
        "Arwen", 
        "Aragorn", 
        "Eowyn", 
        "Gandalf"
      ],
      answer: "Arwen"
    },
    //8
    {
      question: "What is the name of the volcano that the Ring is thrown into?", 
      options: [
        "Osigiliath", 
        "Cirith Ungul", 
        "Minas Tirith", 
        "Barad Dur"
      ],
      answer: "Barad Dur"
    },
    //9
    {
      question: "What is Samwise's last name?",
      options: [
        "Gaffer", 
        "Baggins", 
      "Bronzebeard", 
        "Gamgee"
      ], 
      answer: "Gamgee"
    },
    //10
    {
      question: "What is the name of the local pub in Hobbiton?",
      options: [
        "The Black  Boar", 
        "The Prancing   Pony", 
        "Goldshire  Tavern", 
        "The Green  Dragon"
      ],
      answer: "The Green Dragon"
    },
    //11
    {
      question: "What is Legolas' last name?",
      options: [
        "Stormborn", 
        "Lightfeet", 
        "Greenleaf", 
        "Celebron"
      ],
      answer: "Greenleaf"
    },
    //12
    {
      question: "What causes Merry and Pippin to grow taller than other hobbits?", 
      options: [
        "The magic spells of treebeard", 
        "The Water in Fangorn", 
        "The sorcery of the White Wizard", 
        "The food of the Ents"
      ],
      answer: "The Water in Fangorn"
    },
    //13
    {
      question: "What does Aragorn say right before charging into the last battle in Mordor?",
      options: [
        "It is not this day!", 
        "Hope conquers all!", 
        "Evil will not rule us!", 
        "For Frodo!"
      ],
      answer: "For Frodo!"
    },
    //14
    {
      question: "Which of the following areas in Middle Earth has Legolas NOT been to?",
      options: [
        "Isengard", 
        "Rohan", 
        "The Shire", 
        "Helm's Deep"
      ],
      answer: "The Shire"
    },
    //15
    {
      question: "What feature do Female Dwarves share with Male Dwarves?",
      options: [
        "Beards", 
      "Adam's Apples", 
        "Muscles", 
        "Hairy Chests"
      ],
      answer: "Beards"
    }
  ],
  currentQuestion: 0,
  score: 0
};
